Guide to the Carl Van Vechten Papers Relating to African American Arts and Letters
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1932–1964; Series IV; 157.31 linear feet
  - Selected Photographic Prints, 12.51 linear feet
    - Oversize Mounted Photographic Prints, 110 linear feet
      - Portraits
        - Daniels, Jimmie, with sculpture, Head of Jimmie Daniels, by Richmond Barthé, 1938 December 21; 1 photographic print (Box 161, Folder 2968)
        - Daniels, Jimmie, with sculpture, Head of Jimmie Daniels, by Richmond Barthé, 1938 December 21; 1 photographic print (Box 161, Folder 2969)
        - Davis, Ossie, 1951 April 12; 1 photographic print (Box 162, Folder 2970)
        - Davy, Gloria, in Aida, an opera by Giuseppe Verdi with libretto by Antonio Ghislanzoni, 1958 February 22; 1 photographic print (Box 162, Folder 2971)
        - Dawson, William L. (William Levi), 1934 November 21; 2 photographic prints (Box 162, Folder 2972-2973)
        - De Lavallade, Carmen, 1955 March 3; 1 photographic print (Box 162, Folder 2974)
        - De Lavallade, Carmen, and Geoffrey Holder, 1955 March 3; 1 photographic print (Box 162, Folder 2975)
        - De Paur, Leonard, at the opening of The Art of the Negro in Dance, Music and Drama exhibition at the Museum of the City of New York, 1958 June 17; 1 photographic print (Box 162, Folder 2976)
        - Dee, Ruby, 1961 November 15; 1 photographic print (Box 162, Folder 2977)
        - Dee, Ruby, 1962 September 25; 1 photographic print (Box 162, Folder 2978)
        - Delaney, Beauford, 1953 March 18; 1 photographic print (Box 162, Folder 2979)
        - Delaney, Hubert Thomas "Hap", 1935 March 22; 2 photographic prints (Box 163, Folder 2980-2981)
        - Demby, William, 1956 March 13; 1 photographic print (Box 163, Folder 2982)
        - Dilworth, Hubert, 1963 August 28; 1 photographic print (Box 163, Folder 2983)
        - Dixon, Dean, 1941 September 17; 4 photographic prints (Box 163, Folder 2984-2987)
        - Dobbs, Mattiwilda, 1955 January 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 163, Folder 2988-2989)
        - Douglas, Aaron, 1933 April 10; 2 photographic prints (Box 164, Folder 2990-2991)
        - Du Bois, W. E. B. (William Edward Burghardt), 1946 July 18; 1 photographic print (Box 164, Folder 2992)
        - Dunham, Katherine, 1940 May 10; 1 photographic print (Box 164, Folder 2993)
        - Dunham, Katherine, 1940 May 10; 3 photographic prints (Box 164, Folder 2994-2996)
        - Dunn, Blanche, 1934 January 9; 3 photographic prints (Box 164, Folder 2997-2999)
          Inscription misidentifies her as Blanche Dunne.
        - Dunn, Blanche, 1941 May 10; 4 photographic prints (Box 164, Folder 3000-3003)
        - Eaton, Roy, 1958 December 2; 1 photographic print (Box 165, Folder 3004)
        - Edward, Jon, in The Firebird, ballet by Igor Stravinsky and choreographed by Michel Fokine, 1938 March 25; 2 photographic prints (Box 165, Folder 3005-3006)
        - Elzy, Ruby, as Serena in Porgy and Bess, musical composed by George Gershwin, libretto by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, 1935 December 30; 1 photographic print (Box 165, Folder 3007)
        - Elzy, Ruby, as Serena in Porgy and Bess, musical composed by George Gershwin, libretto by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, 1935 December 30; 1 photographic print (Box 165, Folder 3008)
        - Evans, Bobby, 1942 March 19; 1 photographic print (Box 165, Folder 3009)
        - Fitzgerald, Ella, 1940 January 19; 5 photographic prints (Box 165, Folder 3010-3014)
        - Flowers, Martha, 1953 February 17; 1 photographic print (Box 166, Folder 3015)
        - Garland, Bennie, Jr., 1939 April 23; 1 photographic print (Box 166, Folder 3016)
        - Gibson, Althea, 1958 November 20; 1 photographic print (Box 166, Folder 3017)
        - Gibson, Althea, 1958 November 20; 2 photographic prints (Box 166, Folder 3018-3019)
        - Gibson, Richard, 1959 January 20; 1 photographic print (Box 166, Folder 3020)
        - Gillespie, Dizzy, 1955 December 2; 1 photographic print (Box 166, Folder 3021)
        - Gordon, Taylor, 1933 March 18; 3 photographic prints (Box 166, Folder 3022-3024)
        - Green, Lil, 1942 March 19; 1 photographic print (Box 166, Folder 3025)
        - Grist, Reri, 1959 December 8; 1 photographic print (Box 166, Folder 3026)
        - Guillén, Nicolás, 1949 March 23; 1 photographic print (Box 166, Folder 3027)
        - Hall, Juanita, as Bloody Mary in South Pacific, musical composed by Richard Rodgers with lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, and book by Oscar Hammerstein II and Joshua Logan, 1949 June 25; 2 photographic prints (Box 167, Folder 3028-3029)
        - Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), 1932 May 24; 3 photographic prints (Box 167, Folder 3030-3032)
        - Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), 1941 June 30; 2 photographic prints (Box 167, Folder 3033-3034)
        - Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), 1941 July 17; 3 photographic prints (Box 167, Folder 3035-3037)
        - Harvey, Georgette, 1932 May 23; 1 photographic print (Box 167, Folder 3038)
        - Hawkins, Barry, and Veronica Tyler, 1961 April 11; 1 photographic print (Box 167, Folder 3039)
        - Hayes, Afrika, 1964 March 24; 1 photographic print (Box 167, Folder 3040)
        - Hayes, Marion, 1962 November 20; 1 photographic print (Box 168, Folder 3041)
        - Hayes, Roland, 1954 January 29; 2 photographic prints (Box 168, Folder 3042-3043)
        - Headley, Godfrey, 1959 December 15; 1 photographic print (Box 168, Folder 3044)
        - Himes, Chester B., 1946 March 8; 1 photographic print (Box 168, Folder 3045)
        - Himes, Chester B., 1955 June 28; 1 photographic print (Box 168, Folder 3046)
        - Himes, Chester B., 1962 July 10; 1 photographic print (Box 168, Folder 3047)
        - Hines, Altonell, as Commere in Four Saints in Three Acts, musical by Virgil Thomson with a libretto by Gertrude Stein, 1934 March 9; 1 photographic print (Box 168, Folder 3048)
        - Holder, Geoffrey, 1954 September 2; 2 photographic prints (Box 168, Folder 3049-3050)
        - Holiday, Billie, 1949 March 23; 1 photographic print (Box 168, Folder 3051)
        - Holiday, Billie, 1949 March 23; 3 photographic prints (Box 168, Folder 3052-3054)
        - Holloman, Charlotte, 1957 December 6; 1 photographic print (Box 169, Folder 3055)
        - Holt, Nora Douglas, 1932 March 18; 1 photographic print (Box 169, Folder 3056)
        - Holt, Nora Douglas, 1934 October 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 169, Folder 3057-3058)
        - Holt, Nora Douglas, 1937 August 29; 1 photographic print (Box 169, Folder 3059)
        - Holt, Nora Douglas, at Harlem, New York City, 1932 February 27; 1 photographic print (Box 169, Folder 3060)
        - Horne, Lena, at Greenwood Lake, New Jersey, 1941 September 15; 1 photographic print (Box 169, Folder 3061)
        - Horne, Marilyn, and Henry Lewis, 1961 August 22; 1 photographic print (Box 169, Folder 3062)
        - Hughes, Langston, 1932 March 27; 2 photographic prints (Box 169, Folder 3063-3064)
        - Hughes, Langston, 1936 February 29; 4 photographic prints (Box 170, Folder 3065-3068)
        - Hughes, Langston, at 4th Street, Manhattan, New York City, 1939 June 8; 1 photographic print (Box 170, Folder 3069)
        - Hurston, Zora Neale, 1935 April 3; 2 photographic prints (Box 170, Folder 3070-3071)
        - Hurston, Zora Neale, at Chicago, Illinois, 1934 November 9; 2 photographic prints (Box 170, Folder 3072-3073)
        - Hyman, Earle, as Autolycus in The Winter's Tale, play by William Shakespeare, at the American Shakespeare Festival in Stratford, Connecticut, 1958 August 10; 1 photographic print (Box 170, Folder 3074)
        - Hyman, Earle, as Dunois, The Bastard of Orleans, in Saint Joan, play by George Bernard Shaw, 1956 October 10; 2 photographic prints (Box 170, Folder 3075-3076)
        - Hyman, Earle, as Mister Johnson in Mister Johnson, play by Norman Rosten, based on the novel by Joyce Cary, 1956 April 30; 1 photographic print (Box 171, Folder 3077)
        - Hyman, Earle, as Othello in Othello, play by William Shakespeare, 1953 November 17; 1 photographic print (Box 171, Folder 3078)
        - Hyman, Earle, as Prince of Morocco in The Merchant of Venice, play by William Shakespeare, 1953 March 10; 2 photographic prints (Box 171, Folder 3079-3080)
        - Ingram, Rex, 1934 April 22; 3 photographic prints (Box 171, Folder 3081-3083)
        - Jackman, Harold, 1932 September 11; 2 photographic prints (Box 171, Folder 3084-3085)
        - Jackman, Harold, 1933 November 11; 1 photographic print (Box 171, Folder 3086)
        - Jackman, Ivie, 1962 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 172, Folder 3087)
        - Jackson, Mahalia, 1962 April 16; 1 photographic print (Box 172, Folder 3088)
        - Jackson, Mahalia, 1962 April 16; 1 photographic print (Box 172, Folder 3089)
        - Jackson, Raymond, 1964 March 10; 1 photographic print (Box 172, Folder 3090)
        - Johnson, Charles Spurgeon, 1948 January 21; 1 photographic print (Box 172, Folder 3091)
        - Johnson, Grace Nail, 1932 December 3; 1 photographic print (Box 172, Folder 3092)
        - Johnson, Hall, 1947 May 14; 1 photographic print (Box 172, Folder 3093)
        - Johnson, J. Rosamond (John Rosamond), 1933 April 22; 4 photographic prints (Box 172, Folder 3094-3097)
        - Johnson, James Weldon, 1932 December 3; 3 photographic prints (Box 173, Folder 3098-3100)
        - Johnson, James Weldon, at his home, Five Acres, Great Barrington, Massachusetts, 1936 July 15; 6 photographic prints (Box 173, Folder 3101-3106)
        - Johnson, Mildred, 1937 June 16; 1 photographic print (Box 173, Folder 3107)
        - Jones, James Earl, 1961 May 29; 1 photographic print (Box 173, Folder 3108)
        - Jones, Laurence Clifton, 1955 November 1; 1 photographic print (Box 174, Folder 3109)
        - Jones, Robert Earl, as Young Man in Don't You Want To Be Free?, musical pageant by Langston Hughes, 1938 June 23; 2 photographic prints (Box 174, Folder 3110-3111)
          Inscription identifies him as Earl Jones.
        - Kahloah, 1936 January 28; 1 photographic print (Box 174, Folder 3112)
        - Kahloah, 1936 January 28; 6 photographic prints (Box 174, Folder 3113-3118)
        - Kay, Ulysses, 1947 November 13; 1 photographic print (Box 174, Folder 3119)
        - Kelley, William Melvin, 1963 April 23; 1 photographic print (Box 174, Folder 3120)
        - Kennard, Lawaune, in Black Ritual (Obeah ), ballet choreographed by Agnes de Mille, music by Darius Milhaud, 1940 April 8; 1 photographic print (Box 174, Folder 3121)
        - Killens, John Oliver, 1954 June 8; 2 photographic prints (Box 175, Folder 3122-3123)
        - Kitt, Eartha, 1952 October 19; 2 photographic prints (Box 175, Folder 3124-3125)
        - Kykunkor (The Witch Woman), opera by Asadata Dafora. Unidentified cast member, drummer, 1935 January 17; 3 photographic prints (Box 175, Folder 3126-3128)
        - Lamming, George, 1955 May 24; 1 photographic print (Box 175, Folder 3129)
        - Larsen, Nella, 1932 August 17; 1 photographic print (Box 175, Folder 3130)
        - Larsen, Nella, 1934 November 23; 1 photographic print (Box 175, Folder 3131)
        - Lawrence, Jacob Armstead, 1941 July 31; 2 photographic prints (Box 175, Folder 3132-3133)
        - Lee, Alyne Dumas, 1953 November 16; 1 photographic print (Box 175, Folder 3134)
        - Lee, Canada, as Bigger Thomas in Native Son, play by Paul Green and Richard Wright, 1941 April 7; 1 photographic print (Box 176, Folder 3135)
        - Lee, Canada, as Bigger Thomas in Native Son, play by Paul Green and Richard Wright, 1941 April 7; 2 photographic prints (Box 176, Folder 3136-3137)
        - Lee, Everett, 1948 November 12; 1 photographic print (Box 176, Folder 3138)
        - Locke, Alain, 1941 July 23; 1 photographic print (Box 176, Folder 3139)
        - Long, Avon, as Sportin' Life in Porgy and Bess, musical composed by George Gershwin, libretto by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, 1942 March 24; 1 photographic print (Box 176, Folder 3140)
        - Louis, Joe, at Greenwood Lake, New York and New Jersey, 1941 September 15; 3 photographic prints (Box 176, Folder 3141-3143)
        - Louis, Joe, at Greenwood Lake, New York and New Jersey, 1941 September 15; 6 photographic prints (Box 177, Folder 3144-3149)
        - Lowe, James V., 1963 November 12; 1 photographic print (Box 177, Folder 3150)
        - Major, Gerri, 1935 March 22; 1 photographic print (Box 177, Folder 3151)
          Inscription identifies her as Geraldyn.
        - Maloney, Clyde, 1960 September 21; 1 photographic print (Box 177, Folder 3152)
          Roll number XV rr.
        - Marshall, William, as God in The Green Pastures, play by Marc Connelly adapted from Ol' Man Adam an' His Chillun by Roark Bradford, 1951 April 12; 1 photographic print (Box 177, Folder 3153)
        - Matthews, Edward, as Saint Ignatius of Loyola in Four Saints in Three Acts, musical by Virgil Thomson with a libretto by Gertrude Stein, 1934 March 9; 4 photographic prints (Box 178, Folder 3154-3157)
        - Mayfield, Julian, 1959 March 6; 1 photographic print (Box 178, Folder 3158)
        - Maynor, Dorothy, 1939 September 23; 5 photographic prints (Box 178, Folder 3159-3163)
        - McBurnie, Beryl, wearing a costume from Africa, 1941 July 31; 1 photographic print (Box 179, Folder 3164)
        - McBurnie, Beryl, wearing a costume from Martinique, 1941 July 31; 2 photographic prints (Box 179, Folder 3165-3166)
        - McBurnie, Beryl, wearing a costume from Trinidad, 1941 July 31; 1 photographic print (Box 179, Folder 3167)
        - McClendon, Rose, 1932 February 27; 2 photographic prints (Box 179, Folder 3168-3169)
        - McClendon, Rose, as Medea in Medea, play adapted by Countee Cullen from a play by Euripides, 1935 November 19; 1 photographic print (Box 179, Folder 3170)
        - McFerrin, Robert, 1955 February 28; 1 photographic print (Box 179, Folder 3171)
        - McKay, Claude, 1934 April 13; 3 photographic prints (Box 179, Folder 3172-3174)
        - McKay, Claude, 1941 July 25; 4 photographic prints (Box 180, Folder 3175-3178)
        - McNeil, Claudia, as Mamie in Simply Heavenly, musical with book and lyrics by Langston Hughes and music by David Martin, 1957 June 10; 1 photographic print (Box 180, Folder 3179)
        - McTeer, Kenneth, 1942 November 29; 1 photographic print (Box 180, Folder 3180)
        - Meadows, Allen Juante, 1940 February 7; 3 photographic prints (Box 180, Folder 3181-3183)
        - Meadows, Allen Juante, 1940 March 13; 1 photographic print (Box 180, Folder 3184)
        - Meeres, Paul, 1932 April 1; 5 photographic prints (Box 181, Folder 3185-3189)
        - Meeres, Paul, wearing Roman soldier's costume from dance number at Connie's Inn, 1932 April 1; 1 photographic print (Box 181, Folder 3190)
        - Mercer, Mabel, 1963 May 28; 1 photographic print (Box 181, Folder 3191)
        - Miles, Lizzie, 1957 June 20; 1 photographic print (Box 181, Folder 3192)
        - Mitchell, Arthur, 1955 December 20; 1 photographic print (Box 181, Folder 3193)
        - Mittelholzer, Edgar, 1952 November 13; 1 photographic print (Box 181, Folder 3194)
        - Moon, Mollie, 1956 December 11; 1 photographic print (Box 182, Folder 3195)
        - Moore, Al, 1936 January 28; 1 photographic print (Box 182, Folder 3196)
        - Moore, Leon, 1952 September 22; 1 photographic print (Box 182, Folder 3197)
        - Motley, Willard, 1947 June 13; 1 photographic print (Box 182, Folder 3198)
        - Norman, Madie, 1951 September 23; 1 photographic print (Box 182, Folder 3199)
        - Nugent, Bruce, 1936 February 16; 2 photographic prints (Box 182, Folder 3200-3201)
        - Nurse, Godfrey, 1959 October 20; 1 photographic print (Box 183, Folder 3202)
        - O'Neal, Frederick, at the opening of The Art of the Negro in Dance, Music and Drama exhibition at the Museum of the City of New York, 1958 June 17; 1 photographic print (Box 183, Folder 3203)
        - Parker, Louise, 1963 April 22; 1 photographic print (Box 183, Folder 3204)
        - Perkins, Esther, 1941 April 7; 1 photographic print (Box 183, Folder 3205)
        - Perkins, Esther, and Loretta Perkins, 1941 April 7; 1 photographic print (Box 183, Folder 3206)
        - Perkins, Julius, Jr., 1939 July 22; 1 photographic print (Box 183, Folder 3207)
        - Perkins, Julius, Jr., 1939 July 22; 1 photographic print (Box 183, Folder 3208)
        - Perkins, Julius, Jr., 1941 July 15; 2 photographic prints (Box 183, Folder 3209-3210)
        - Perkins, Mildred, 1937 July 15; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3211)
        - Perry, Charles, 1962 March 14; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3212)
        - Peterson, Dorothy Randolph, 1932 March 26; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3213)
        - Peterson, Dorothy Randolph, 1937 July 11; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3214)
        - Peterson, Dorothy Randolph, and Jerome Sidney Peterson, 1953 December 4; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3215)
        - Peterson, Jerome Bowers, 1939 August 18; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3216)
        - Peterson, Jerome Sidney, 1932 March 26; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3217)
        - Peterson, Jerome Sidney, 1953 December 4; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3218)
        - Peterson, Louis, 1960 August 9; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3219)
        - Peterson, Vera Joseph, 1939 August 18; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3220)
        - Petry, Ann, 1948 November 12; 1 photographic print (Box 184, Folder 3221)
        - Pippin, Horace, at the home of Albert C. (Albert Coombs) Barnes, Lower Merion Township, Pennsylvania, 1940 February 4; 1 photographic print (Box 185, Folder 3222)
        - Pittman, Evelyn La Rue, 1962 September 18; 1 photographic print (Box 185, Folder 3223)
        - Polk, Oscar, 1937 January 24; 1 photographic print (Box 185, Folder 3224)
        - Price, Leontyne, 1951 December 11; 2 photographic prints (Box 185, Folder 3225-3226)
        - Price, Leontyne, 1953 May 19; 2 photographic prints (Box 185, Folder 3227-3228)
        - Rahn, Muriel, as Carmen Jones in Carmen Jones, musical with music by Georges Bizet and book and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, 1944 February 29; 2 photographic prints (Box 185, Folder 3229-3230)
        - Rahn, Muriel, as Cora Lewis in The Barrier, musical with music by Jan Meyerowitz and book and lyrics by Langston Hughes, 1950 January 29; 1 photographic print (Box 185, Folder 3231)
        - Ramsay, Edith, 1933 November 29; 2 photographic prints (Box 185, Folder 3232-3233)
        - Reading, Bertice, 1959 January 6; 1 photographic print (Box 186, Folder 3234)
        - Richer, Clément, at Paris, France, 1949 October 9; 1 photographic print (Box 186, Folder 3235)
        - Robeson, Eslanda Goode, 1933 June 1; 2 photographic prints (Box 186, Folder 3236-3237)
        - Robeson, Eslanda Goode, 1936 January 10; 1 photographic print (Box 186, Folder 3238)
        - Robeson, Eslanda Goode, 1945 February 15; 1 photographic print (Box 186, Folder 3239)
        - Robeson, Paul, 1932 March 7; 5 photographic prints (Box 186, Folder 3240-3244)
        - Robeson, Paul, 1933 June 1; 7 photographic prints (Box 187, Folder 3245-3251)
        - Robeson, Paul, as Othello in Othello, play by William Shakespeare, 1944 June 1; 1 photographic print (Box 187, Folder 3252)
        - Robeson, Paul, Jr., 1935 February 15; 4 photographic prints (Box 187, Folder 3253-3256)
        - Robinson, Bill, 1933 January 25; 5 photographic prints (Box 188, Folder 3257-3261)
        - Robinson, Bill, 1933 January 25; 7 photographic prints (Box 188, Folder 3262-3268)
        - Robinson, Bill, 1941 April 18; 4 photographic prints (Box 189, Folder 3269-3272)
        - Robinson, Bill, 1941 April 18; 4 photographic prints (Box 189, Folder 3273-3276)
        - Robinson, Bill, 1941 April 18; 7 photographic prints (Box 190, Folder 3277-3283)
        - Robinson-Wayne, Beatrice, 1935 April 5; 1 photographic print (Box 190, Folder 3284)
        - Robinson-Wayne, Beatrice, as St. Theresa I in Four Saints in Three Acts, musical by Virgil Thomson with a libretto by Gertrude Stein, 1934 March 9; 1 photographic print (Box 190, Folder 3285)
        - Robinson-Wayne, Beatrice, as St. Theresa I in Four Saints in Three Acts, musical by Virgil Thomson with a libretto by Gertrude Stein, 1934 March 9; 4 photographic prints (Box 190, Folder 3286-3289)
        - Rodgers, Guy, 1958 May 24; 1 photographic print (Box 191, Folder 3290)
        - Rodriguez, Percy, 1960 June 7; 1 photographic print (Box 191, Folder 3291)
        - Sampson, Edith S. (Edith Spurlock), 1949 April 6; 1 photographic print (Box 191, Folder 3292)
        - Sands, Diana, 1963 January 29; 1 photographic print (Box 191, Folder 3293)
        - Savage, Archie, 1942 March 2; 1 photographic print (Box 191, Folder 3294)
        - Schuyler, George S. (George Samuel), 1941 July 2; 2 photographic prints (Box 191, Folder 3295-3296)
        - Schuyler, Philippa, 1946 July 22; 1 photographic print (Box 191, Folder 3297)
        - Schuyler, Philippa, 1951 May 9; 1 photographic print (Box 191, Folder 3298)
        - Scott, Harold, 1959 February 17; 1 photographic print (Box 191, Folder 3299)
        - Shirley, George, 1961 October 10; 1 photographic print (Box 192, Folder 3300)
        - Short, Bobby, 1962 January 3; 1 photographic print (Box 192, Folder 3301)
        - Showers, Pearl, 1933 May 20; 1 photographic print (Box 192, Folder 3302)
        - Simpson, Merton D. (Merton Daniel), 1959 September 1; 1 photographic print (Box 192, Folder 3303)
        - Sissle, Noble, 1951 November 20; 2 photographic prints (Box 192, Folder 3304-3305)
        - Smith, Bessie, 1936 February 3; 5 photographic prints (Box 192, Folder 3306-3310)
        - Smith, William Gardner, 1948 December 10; 1 photographic print (Box 193, Folder 3311)
        - Spearman, Rawn W. (Rawn Wardell), 1952 January 12; 1 photographic print (Box 193, Folder 3312)
        - Still, William Grant, 1949 March 12; 1 photographic print (Box 193, Folder 3313)
        - Stinnett, McCleary, 1933 April 22; 3 photographic prints (Box 193, Folder 3314-3316)
        - Stokes, Al, 1934 March 30; 1 photographic print (Box 193, Folder 3317)
        - Stokes, Al, as Heywood Parsons in They Shall Not Die, play by John Wexley, 1934 March 30; 4 photographic prints (Box 194, Folder 3318-3321)
        - Strayhorn, Billy, 1958 August 19; 1 photographic print (Box 194, Folder 3322)
        - Sullivan, Maxine, 1941 October 7; 2 photographic prints (Box 194, Folder 3323-3324)
        - Swanson, Howard, 1951 April 4; 1 photographic print (Box 194, Folder 3325)
        - Tann, Wesley, 1962 May 1; 1 photographic print (Box 194, Folder 3326)
        - Thayer, Alonzo, 1933 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 194, Folder 3327)
        - Thayer, Alonzo, 1933 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 194, Folder 3328)
        - Thomas, Edna, 1932 June 18; 2 photographic prints (Box 195, Folder 3329-3330)
        - Thompson, Claude, as Islander in Jamaica, musical with music by Harold Arlen and book by E.Y. Harburg and Fred Saidy, 1959 February 5; 1 photographic print (Box 195, Folder 3331)
        - Tuguese as Chief Burah in Kykunkor (The Witch Woman), opera by Asadata Dafora, 1935 January 14; 4 photographic prints (Box 195, Folder 3332-3335)
        - Tynes, Margaret, 1959 September 14; 2 photographic prints (Box 195, Folder 3336-3337)
        - Tynes, Margaret, 1959 September 23; 1 photographic print (Box 195, Folder 3338)
        - Valentine, Grace, 1932 April 13; 1 photographic print (Box 195, Folder 3339)
        - Van Dyke, Henry, 1961 September 26; 1 photographic print (Box 196, Folder 3340)
        - Victor, Sarah, 1933 May 12; 2 photographic prints (Box 196, Folder 3341-3342)
        - Wallace, Emmett Babe, 1943 January 6; 1 photographic print (Box 196, Folder 3343)